<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Application on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Description</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/description/</guid>
      <description>Often, you not only want to test knowledge, but its application too. This can be done in online exams, for example in the form of open-ended questions. Other options are open book exams or case study exams. Although these are less susceptible to cheating in their online form than exams with multiple choice questions alone, they are more labour-intensive. They are therefore more likely to be an option if you have help, such as a student assistant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/how/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/how/</guid>
      <description>For groups of more than 100 students, an exam with open-ended questions alone is often inefficient.
If both knowledge and its application need to be assessed, you can reduce the workload by using a mixture of multiple-choice or fill-in-the-blank questions and open-ended questions. You can also use item banks or standard model answers, which only require the examiner to scan for certain terms.
Assessing presentations, projects or products can be very time-consuming, which is why this method may not seem to be an obvious choice at this scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/large/application/tips/</guid>
      <description>Set a suitable time limit: too much time increases the risk of cheating, but too little time causes stress and reduces the validity of the exam results. See Van Berkel (1999) (in Dutch) for estimates of the time needed for different types of questions.
 Emphasize the student’s ethical responsibility not to cheat.
 Ensure good communication with the students.
 Be transparent about the online assessment process, so that students know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
