<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online Presentation on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Online Presentation on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Definition</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/definition/</guid>
      <description>In an online presentation, a student gives a presentation or pitch on a certain subject, either individually or as a group, using video conferencing software. The student may also use presentation tools, drawings, plans or models during the presentation. The presentation can be given live or can be pre-recorded, and there may be time during or after the presentation for questions. Presentations are suitable for assessing the following levels of cognitive learning: remembering, understanding, applying, analysing, evaluating and creating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/online/</guid>
      <description>Students need different skills to give an online presentation. As well as the ability to use video conferencing software, the presentation may also need to be adapted to the online setting. A physical poster presentation really is a different activity when done online.
Advantages *Can be done live or can be pre-recorded. *Location-independent. *Can simulate a real-life professional setting.
Disadvantages *Limited reliability if there is just one examiner. *Risk of technical problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/approach/</guid>
      <description>Preparation Assessment form If a presentation is to be given online, you may need to make some changes to the assessment form as not every criterion can be assessed online. For example, it is difficult to judge whether the student manages to hold the audience’s attention.
Anticipate technical problems Organising online presentations differs somewhat from organising presentations face-to-face. As well as the &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; information (about planning, procedure, equipment, expectations, assessment method), you also need to communicate the ground rules for working on the online platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/tips/</guid>
      <description>*Give students the opportunity to practice an online presentation by planning an online session in which students can practice with each other. Make sure that they have a copy of the assessment form and let them give each other feedback based on the form. The students learn a lot about their own performance through peer feedback, improve their capacity for self-reflection and inspire each other. See this brochure by Inholland (in Dutch) for more information on organising peer feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/presentation/references/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
