<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projecten or Product on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projecten or Product on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Definition</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/definition/</guid>
      <description>With projects and products, students can apply what they have learned in an active and practical manner, and within set boundaries. This improves their understanding of the subject. Projects and products are suitable for assessing whether a student can create and apply, analyse and evaluate knowledge.
However, projects and products are less suitable for assessing whether a student has a broad knowledge base. In practice, projects and products are often combined with other types of assessment that are more suited to this, such as exams with open-ended and/or closed-ended questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/online/</guid>
      <description>With a project or product, a student carries out a clearly-defined assignment. Projects often result in a product such as an analysis, recommendation, design, final product or essay:
*Analysis The student analyses a situation, problem or issue, separating the main issues from the side issues and/or identifying the advantages and disadvantages. *Recommendation A recommendation is often the result of an analysis. The student collates information from various sources to come up with a recommendation and a possible solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/approach/</guid>
      <description>Preparation The preparation required for online projects and products does not differ very much from that required in ‘regular’ education. You first need to identify which learning objectives are to be achieved by the student. You then design an assignment that ensures that the students can demonstrate that they have achieved these objectives, for example in the form of products. You also set the boundaries within which the project or product must be completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/tips/</guid>
      <description>Organise an online peer feedback session well before the submission date for the final draft version of a project/product. Using the assessment form, the students can give each other feedback on their products. This saves you time, as many common mistakes will be picked up and solved by the students.
 *Facilitate and encourage self-management in students as they work on a project. For example, have students set themselves personal goals in their project and let them reflect on these goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/project_product/references/</guid>
      <description>VU guidelines on variations on written assignments. Toetsen in het hogeronderwijs (Assessment in higher education, in Dutch) (Van Berkel, Bax, and Joosten-ten Brinke 2017), about the importance of feedback in the learning process. Toetswijzer competentiegericht begeleiden &amp;amp; beoordelen in het hoger onderwijs (Assessment guidelines, competence-focused supervision and assessment in higher education, in Dutch). Fontys facilities company, department of education: Centre for education innovation and research. Peer assessment als leermiddel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
