<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oral Exam on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oral Exam on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Definition</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/definition/</guid>
      <description>An oral exam is an exam in which a student answers questions orally or gives a pitch/presentation. Oral exams are suitable for assessing the following levels of cognitive learning: remembering, understanding, applying, analysing, evaluating and creating.
Oral exams are often combined with other assessment methods. Often, an online oral exam takes place following submission of a portfolio, project, product or presentation. During an online oral exam, a student may also be allowed to give a short online presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/online/</guid>
      <description>Online assessment interview During an online assessment interview, the examiner asks the student questions based on predetermined criteria, using video conferencing software. These could be questions about situations that show that the student has acquired certain skills and competences. The examiner may also ask follow-up questions. Often, an online assessment interview takes place following the submission of a portfolio, project/product or presentation. During an online assessment interview, the student may be allowed to give a short online presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/approach/</guid>
      <description>Preparation Questions The questions that you ask during an online assessment interview or oral exam are no different from those that you would ask face-to-face. You can also use images such as an anatomical or technical drawing, or a model.
Anticipating technical problems The organisation does differ from a face-to-face oral exam. As well as the &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; information (about planning, procedure, equipment, expectations, assessment method), you also need to communicate the ground rules for working on the online platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/tips/</guid>
      <description>*Carry out assessment interviews in groups, so that students can look at each other&amp;rsquo;s products before the interview, ask questions and provide peer feedback. The examiner can of course also ask questions and give feedback. See this brochure by Inholland (in Dutch) for more information on organising peer feedback. *Give students the opportunity to practice an assessment interview by planning an online meeting in which students can practice with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/oral_exam/references/</guid>
      <description>When old becomes new (Akimov and Malin 2020) describes how online oral exams can be used as an online assessment tool or to supplement other assessment tools. The online oral exam is mainly used as an interview. Tips are provided for ensuring the reliability and validity of this form of online assessment. An article (in Dutch) by the Open University on online oral exams. This article describes the main procedural aspects of online oral exams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
