<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knowlegde on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knowlegde on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Description</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/description/</guid>
      <description>One method for assessing knowledge is a multiple-choice exam with open-ended questions.
This form of online assessment has some clear advantages, because the answers are standardised and can be, at least partly, marked online. It also resolves the problem of illegible handwriting. Online assessment also means that the exam can be taken at any time and location. You therefore do not have to arrange a room and it costs students less in termsof time and travel expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/how/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/how/</guid>
      <description>Assessing knowledge in an online exam is more susceptible to cheating. Measures therefore need to be taken to counter this. Online assessment software can provide tools for preventing cheating as much as possible. For example, the software may turn off certain functions on the computer so that students cannot open an external web page.
Online proctoring can also be used. Live proctoring means that an examiner is present in the video conference to monitor students in real time, for example via a webcam or telephone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/small/knowledge/tips/</guid>
      <description>Set a suitable time limit: too much time increases the risk of cheating, but too little time causes stress and reduces the validity of the exam results. See Van Berkel (1999) (in Dutch) for estimates of the time needed for different types of questions.
 Emphasize the student’s ethical responsibility not to cheat.
 Ensure good communication with the students.
 Be transparent about the online assessment process, so that students know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
