<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Observations on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Observations on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Definition</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/definition/</guid>
      <description>During an observation, a student is observed while carrying out a certain task. For example, a student may have to conduct a performance appraisal, insert a catheter, use a pipette, perform a dance, or give a lesson. An observation can take place in a real-life or a simulated setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/online/</guid>
      <description>An online observation can be carried out in three ways:
 Watch an online activity live. This could be an activity that needs to be done online (e.g. using a computer programme) or an activity that takes place online for the purpose of assessment (e.g. conducting an interview). The observation can take place at any location. Watch an activity live on-location. The observers watch an activity live at another location (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/approach/</guid>
      <description>Preparation Assessment form An assessment form is usually used when observing students. Make sure to check that all the assessment criteria can be properly assessed online; do you have all the information you need for each criterion as the observer, or will the lack of some information on the screen (e.g. a client’s reaction) make it impossible to assess certain criteria?
Number of observations and observers The main advantage of online observation is that it can take place at any time and location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/tips/</guid>
      <description>*Show the students a few examples of a recorded online observation before they have theirs (e.g. previously submitted recordings), so that they know what is expected, both in terms of content and the recording. This also allows students to compare themselves with what they see in the recording, so that they can judge whether they are ready. *You could ask the students to hand in an unsuccessful version of the activity with the recorded online observation, so that they can learn from their mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/methods/observations/references/</guid>
      <description>Toetsen in het hoger onderwijs (Van Berkel, Bax, and Joosten-ten Brinke 2017) (Assessment in higher education) is a general book about assessment with a chapter on assessment of performance that deals in more detail with the assessment of observable activities. It contains very useful information on ensuring reliability and validity during this form of assessment.  Bibliography Van Berkel, Henk, Anneke Bax, and Desirée Joosten-ten Brinke. 2017. Toetsen in Het Hoger Onderwijs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
