<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recommended assessment methods on Assessment Selection Tool</title>
    <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recommended assessment methods on Assessment Selection Tool</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 11:05:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Assessment</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/digital_assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/digital_assessment/</guid>
      <description>Tips for this assessment method
 If the group of students is too large to be able to use lots of open-ended questions, you could use closed-ended questions with automatic marking. Examples are multiple choice questions, drag-and-drop questions or short essay questions. Note however that this makes it even more important to ensure that students cannot cheat.
 In the case of open-ended questions, set a limit on the number of words, for exaple, or what the answer should include, to prevent long-winded answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Tips for this assessment method
 Assessing presentations, projects or products can be very time-consuming, and may therefore not seem to be an obvious choice at this scale. However, the assessment in a formative setting can be made easier by dividing students into groups and/or implementing peer feedback, in which students assess one another’s work. It may also help to have students record their presentations, so that you can assess them at a more suitable time and location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oral Exam</title>
      <link>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/oral_exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://werkgroep-toetsen-op-afstand.github.io/assessment-selection-tool/en/medium/knowledge/methods/oral_exams/</guid>
      <description>  Tips for this assessment method
 Divide the students into groups for group oral exams, to reduce the time required for assessment.
 In the case of formative assessment, use can be made of peer feedback.
 If the examiner does not know a student, ask the student to hold up their ID card or student card to show who they are.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
